fxnet.com 2015-05-05

# Privacy Policy

                                                                                                          Tel: +357 25 108111
                                                                                                               info@fxnet.com
                                                                                                               www.fxnet.com
                                     Privacy Policy
All informational material collected on this website is held by FxNet Ltd in the strictest confidence. FxNet
Ltd considers one of its highest priorities to be the privacy and integrity of the personal information of its
Clients, and devotes the maximum amount of attention to keeping the said information safely stored as
well as used appropriately and only with the required authorisation. Any and all of the information that is
received from the Client is handled with care and an appropriate level of confidentiality.
FxNet Ltd incorporates strict rules and specific procedures into the day-to-day running of the company in
order to guarantee its Clients the maximum achievable level of security in handling their said information.
All information held by the Company is protected under the Data Protection Act 1998.
Use of Clients Personal Information
The information received from Clients is used by the company in order to confirm the Clients identity at
any given time. This is done in order to minimise the risk of any sort unauthorised and unprecedented
access to the Clients account within the System of the Company.
Other uses of the Clients information include:
       the processing of any trading and/or non-trading operations;
       to be able to maintain a constant and correct database of Client accounts;
       The provision any kind of services that are relevant to the Clients Business relationship with the
        Company;
       carrying out the company’s anti-money laundering policy
Client information is also collected for the purpose of carrying out the Test of Appropriateness; this is
done in order to ensure the Companies Clients are appropriate to undertake the investment services
provided by the Company.
The personal information required includes but is not necessarily limited to the following:
       Name
       Date of Birth
       E-mail
       Address
       Funding Details
       Financial Situation
       Trading Activity
The latter information is required due to the nature of activates and services provided by the Company.
                     Agios Athanasios Avenue, No. 58-60 El Greco Building Flat 202, 4102 Limassol, Cyprus

                                                                                                           Tel: +357 25 108111
                                                                                                                info@fxnet.com
                                                                                                                www.fxnet.com
Third Parties
The Clients personal information may be, in limited amounts, distributed and further used by trusted third
parties, in particular, banks, through which trading operations and the related transactions will take place.
                      Agios Athanasios Avenue, No. 58-60 El Greco Building Flat 202, 4102 Limassol, Cyprus
